What's up, Cowboys Nation? I'm Nick
Eatman here with the newest Cowboys
cornerback, Darian Kendrick. Just signed
this week. How excited are you to be
here with the Cowboys? Um
I can't explain it, for real.
Uh
I kind of started out like this, you
know what I'm saying? So, life coming in
full circle. Uh it's grew up playing for
it, you know what I'm saying? My
my city team, Rock Hill Cowboys. So,
it's like
I'm saying, it's it's like a dream come
true, for real. So, in Little League,
when you were with the Cowboys, is is
that is that the goal one day to play
obviously play in the NFL, but play for
the Cowboys? Cowboys are always that
team that I guess that everyone looks
at. Yeah, America's team. And like, you
know what I'm saying? Growing up, my
aunt like she was forcing it on me, you
know what I'm saying? So,
I was that's Cowboys that's Cowboys
that's Cowboys till I really, you know
what I'm saying? watched football on my
own. But
life is just coming in full circle this,
you know what I'm saying? God's God's
timing, for real. So, what what corner
what type of cornerback are the Cowboys
getting here? How can you kind of
describe your game?
A smart uh feisty, physical, and
ball-aware corner, for sure.
Now,
there's you know, there's a knock on
corners that oh, maybe they don't have
the best hands. You were a receiver,
actually. You started your career as a
receiver. So, you feel like with the
ball in the air it's it's just as much
yours. It's mine, for sure.
Um you played with the Rams, you played
with the Seahawks. They have some really
good receivers over there. So, practices
are probably just as tough as some games
uh going up against Puka and and Jaxon
Smith-Njigba and Davante Adams. Here,
you got some pretty good receivers to go
up in practice as well. Is it one of
those iron sharpens iron type things?
Yeah, that's that's how you got to look
at it as, for real. Uh another day at
work, you know what I'm saying? Just go
in there.
You know I know what I got, you know
what I'm saying? I played against GP in
in college. Well, played with him,
played against him.
Uh
great guy.
You know what I'm saying? Loves to
compete, and you know, I do too. So,
uh we're going to it's going to be some
great practices out there that we'll
we'll get just getting each other better
for those Sundays. Obviously, this
defense needs some improvement. That's
it's been well documented. Christian
Parker is the new defensive coordinator.
What have you heard about what are some
of the changes that the Cowboys defense
is going to make this year?
Need more people that, you know what I'm
saying? That buy in, and not really, you
know what I'm saying? Uh
has too much
ego, you know what I'm saying? Uh and
just want to play for their teammates.
All right. That's the Cowboys' newest
cornerback, Darian Kendrick.